flirtic.com 2017-08-11

# Flirtic.com - Privacy

## Flirtic's Privacy Policy

PLEASE READ THIS DOCUMENT CAREFULLY. IT CONTAINS IMPORTANT INFORMATION THAT YOU SHOULD KNOW BEFORE CONTINUING TO USE OUR SERVICES. BY CONTINUING TO USE FLITRIC'S WEBSITE AND SERVICES YOU WILL BE DEEMED TO HAVE ACCEPTED THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

Flirtic is an online dating and social networking service, provided by website, mobile applications, social networking application and other means. Your privacy is very important to us. We have developed this Privacy Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information. 

This policy and any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with it or its subject matter (including non-contractual disputes or claims) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with laws of State of **Delaware, Unites States of America** without reference to conflicts of law rules or principles. In the event there is a discrepancy between this English language version and any translated copies of the Privacy Policy, the English version shall prevail.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our services or conducting business with us. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe to you our services, the information we collect, how we use that information, with whom it may be shared and your choices about such uses and disclosures. All personal information that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. Flirtic reserves the right to adjust and/or amend this policy from time to time at its sole discretion, but will prominently post any material changes on Flirtic website. You will be given the opportunity to opt-out. If as the result of such changes, you want to alter the ways in which Flirtic is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by editing your preferences in Account Settings section. In order for Flirtic to provide you with our services, it is important for us to collect certain personal information from our users and disclose that information to other users. By accepting this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described by this Privacy Policy. 

Flirtic cannot control, nor be responsible for, information that you post using our services that is misused by other users or other third parties in a way that is not approved by our Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy, or the good spirit of our service. By using Flirtic's services and/or maintaining a Flirtic user account, you are consenting to the practices set out in both Flirtic's Privacy Policy and Terms of Service.

Flirtic reserves the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time and without notice, so be sure to check this Privacy Policy regularly to understand how we use your information.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the end of this Privacy Policy for information on how to contact us.

IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT AND AGREE WITH OUR PRIVACY POLICY THEN YOU MUST NOT ACCESS OR USE OUR SERVICES.

## Who we are

Flirtic is operated by Flirtic Inc., a company registered in Delaware, USA (ALEXANDRIA, 901 N. PITT STREET, SUITE 325).

## Age Restrictions

16 years old and older may register at Flirtic (higher threshold may apply in certain cases and/or countries). Minors, or any person younger than 16, are strictly prohibited. Please do not attempt becoming a member if you are not at least 16 years of age.

## Personally Identifying Information Provided to and Collected by Flirtic

Any information a user shares using Flirtic's services about himself or herself will be deemed a voluntary disclosure of personal information. Personally identifiable information that our site will collect and store may include: age, general geographic location, aim of acquaintance, your education, religion, your native language, smoking habits and information about children. Furthermore, Flirtic will allow a user to voluntarily provide additional personal information, such as, but not limited to: interests, favorite activities, ideal get-togethers. 

Users will also have the option of permitting Flirtic to collect, store, and post your personal information shared on other social networking services. Flirtic will not collect, store, or post this information unless a user has expressly opted-in to this service by agreeing to the “allow access” verification upon signup or by choosing to opt-in to the service post signup. However, Flirtic will not reciprocate – we will not share your information collected via our services or our opted-in access to your other social networking services with those services you have granted us access to.

You never have to answer any questions, and you can decline this exchange of information at any time. However, if you should choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with some of the services dependent upon the collection of this information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. Flirtic will inform you of the mandatory and/or optional character of the requested and/or required information. 

As a registered user you have the right to access and change your personal information and privacy preferences at any time by logging into your personal account, where you can view and make changes to your personal information. 

## Flirtic's Disclosures of Your Information

Aside from the few narrow exceptions directly addressed in this Privacy Policy, the personal information that you share via Flirtic services will be accessible to everyone visiting your Flirtic profile, including users visiting our website as non-registered members. 

Flirtic reserves the right to disclose certain information in the files we maintain about you, and the other information we obtain from your current and past activities at Flirtic, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of Service. At times, we may review the data of multiple members to identify problems or resolve disputes. Flirtic is committed to cooperating with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties, to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. 

By accepting our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service, you authorize us to disclose any information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with any investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose you or us to legal liability. 

Flirtic reserves the right to use your personally identifiable information for internal research, such as to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze Flirtic services usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our services. However, Flirtic does not sell your information to advertisers or other similar third parties for their commercial use.

In the event that all or substantially all of Flirtic's stock and/or all or substantially all assets are transferred or sold to another entity, Flirtic may transfer personally identifiable information to the acquiring entity. If, as a result of such a business transition, your personally identifiable information will be used in a materially different manner, you will be given choice consistent with our policy regarding notification of changes. When you submit personal information to Flirtic, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which Flirtic and its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transferring, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted vendors of Flirtic. Such vendors are bound by contract not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties.

Flirtic services may be subject to the laws of various jurisdictions, because access to Flirtic services may use internet traffic of different jurisdictions, including European Union countries or United States of America. Flirtic will disclose personally identifiable information without your permission when required by law, or in good faith belief that such action is necessary to investigate or protect against harmful activities to Flirtic guests, visitors, associates, or property, or to others. Laws related to personal identifiable information vary by country. 

For example, personally identifiable information collected in the European Union and its Member States is subject to the EU Directives concerning personal data, privacy and electronic communications, including but not limited to Directive 2002/58/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 12 July 2002 concerning the processing of personal data and the protection of privacy in the electronic communications sector and Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data and the subsequent legislation adopted in the EU Member States. Another example, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) was passed by the U.S. Congress in November 1998. COPPA provides parents with specific rights regarding their children's privacy. For additional information and resources on COPPA, please visit the Federal Trade Commission website at http://www.ftc.gov/. Any products or services provided by Flirtic are not directed at children under 13 years of age and, therefore, COPPA does not apply directly. However, we recognize that children under the age of 13 may access our services without Flirtic's consent. The collection of this information is covered above. Parents or Legal Guardians may request from us to review, delete or stop the collection of the personally identifiable information of their child. You may do so emailing us at support@flirtic.com. Flirtic may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information to appropriate governmental authorities. If requested by law enforcement or judicial authorities, we will provide this information upon receipt of the appropriate documentation. Flirtic may also provide information to law enforcement to protect its property and the health and safety of individuals as permitted by statute.

## Password

Individuals signing up for Flirtic may be given the opportunity to create a unique password to use as an identifier and login. This password will be protected by system administrators and will not be intentionally shared with third parties under any circumstances. 

This assists the system administrators in protecting your information. In some cases, such as registration with your other social networks accounts, additional password may not be required. 

## E-Mail

Flirtic may use the information you provide to contact you regarding Flirtic, as well as for billing purposes should you opt into a paid service. Flirtic will not send unsolicited commercial e-mail unrelated to Flirtic, nor will Flirtic share your e-mail address with third parties. We don't share your personal information to third parties and any third party offers can be managed by you in your Account Settings section. The e-mails we send to you may contain code, which allows Flirtic to track usage of the e-mail, including whether the e-mail was opened and/or what links (if any) were clicked.

## Financial Information

Flirtic may accept credit and debit cards, as well as other payment methods, for billing purposes should you opt into a paid service. Please note that we do not store any credit card or other payment card details. However, our payment service providers do (and are approved to do so by all applicable regulatory bodies). No access is permitted to this information by any third party. 

Unless expressly provided to the contrary, personal information that you provide while you are visiting a provider's website will be subject to the privacy policy posted on such site, and personal information that you provide while on this website in conjunction with a provider's service will be subject to this Privacy Policy. For instance, the credit card information entered as part of the filling out the purchase form or registration process is collected by the third parties registration and/or merchant services and subject to their respective privacy policies. 

## Browser Information

Flirtic does not collect personally identifiable information from your computer when you browse the website and request pages from our servers. However, Flirtic may log IP addresses for systems administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a user's session, to identify problems in development, investigate fraudulent use of Flirtic services, and for other reasons at our discretion. We also use this information to better understand how visitors use our services and how we can better tune our services' contents and functionality to meet your needs.

## Cookies

Cookies are required to use Flirtic's website properly. Flirtic uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A cookie is a small data file that can include an anonymous unique identifier that is stored on the computer hard drive of the user. Session cookies are temporary cookies that remain in a file of the browser until logged out of the website. Session cookies do not store any personally identifying information, only a unique visitor ID that is used to improve the Flirtic user experience. Persistent cookies remain in the cookie file of the browser after leaving the Flirtic website. Persistent cookies also do not store any personally identifiable information, only preferences such as "Remember Me" so users do not have to log in to the site for every visit. 

Please be aware that cookies may be required to complete certain functions on the Flirtic website. Flirtic makes no warranties of site performance if the user changes browser settings or employs other actions to disable cookies. Flirtic will not allow third parties to place or recognize cookies on your browser while you are browsing Flirtic website.

## Security

Flirtic will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between the user's computer and Flirtic's servers, and the storage of information on those servers. However, Flirtic cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to Flirtic over the Internet and accepts no liability for any unintentional disclosure. Flirtic also cannot ensure or warrant the security or stability of any user's computer for reasons including, but not limited to, viruses or other types of malware. Statements made in this Privacy Policy, regarding Flirtic's privacy policies, are only intended to apply to intentional disclosures. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users. 

## Limitation of Liability

Flirtic services are created solely for the use of sixteen (16) years of age and older (higher threshold may apply in certain cases and/or countries). As such, Flirtic services are not suitable for children. Flirtic, while acting in accordance with the laws, will not be responsible for inaccuracies or completeness of user profiles. When aware of a user who has created an inaccurate profile, Flirtic will take appropriate action to correct the issue according to the Terms of Service. Flirtic makes no representation or warranty regarding the accuracy or completeness thereof. Use of Flirtic services is at the risk of the user, and Flirtic disclaims all responsibility for any loss, injury, or other damage that might be suffered in consequence of any reliance upon or exposure to any part of this site.

## Opt-Out

To deactivate their profile from our database, users may sign in and deactivate their profile. These options are available from “Account Settings” page. If you want to stop using your account, you have two options. You can temporarily deactivate your account and you can remove your account completely. Removing your account means that no user will be able to search for you on Flirtic, although they may still see you profile from direct cached links. Your deactivated account will be completely deleted within 48 hours. Many users want to deactivate their accounts for temporary reasons and in doing so expect us to maintain their information until they return to Flirtic. You can temporarily close your account for 90 days, after that period your account will be reinstalled again and you will be notified about that by e-mail. To prevent abuse and/or misuse of Flirtic by a user following termination or deletion of a profile/account we shall retain such information as we deem in our sole discretion may be necessary to ensure that user does not open a new account and profile in breach of our Terms of Service and to ensure compliance with all laws and regulations.

**Warning:** Even after you deactivate your account, copies of that information may still be viewable and/or accessed on the Internet to the extent such information has been previously shared with others, or copied or stored by other users or to the extent such information has been shared with search engines. We cannot control these activities, and therefore do not accept any responsibility for such exchange of information. If you have given third party applications or websites access to your personal information they may retain such information to the extent permitted under their terms of service or privacy policies.

## Correcting and Updating Information

Once logged in, go to your Flirtic profile; all fields will be editable at this stage.

## Contacting Flirtic

Users with any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of Flirtic services, or any dealings with Flirtic are encouraged to contact the Site Administrator by emailing support@flirtic.com 

## Policy Changes

If Flirtic makes any changes to the Privacy Policy, Effective Date of the latest update of this Privacy Policy will be updated. Flirtic reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, at its sole discretion, but will prominently post any material changes on the website, so users are invited to review it frequently. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy by your continued use of Flirtic services after such notice has been posted for thirty (30) days with the following exception: if at the time you provide personal information to Flirtic you limit how such information will be used to communicate with you, either by Flirtic or by third parties, Flirtic will not change your preference in this regard without your express consent. Users' continued use of any portion of Flirtic services following an email and/or posting of the updated privacy statement will constitute acceptance of the changes.

## Acceptance of the Privacy Statement

Users' use of Flirtic's website or any other services, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this privacy statement. **BY USING FLIRTIC SERVICES, USERS ARE ACCEPTING AND CONSENTING TO THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS POLICY.**

## Effective Date

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 28.10.2014. Copyright © 2017 Flirtic OÜ. All rights reserved
